{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"0a817f6c-2947-4935-942f-e53be3210d6a"},"exam":{"id":"4f00da52-4535-42ac-981b-35fcc6e32347","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"f3458221-d64a-4bbb-b337-65aa47b1614e","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following does Amazon assure will happen when paying for AWS on an as-needed basis?","explanation":"Amazon provides certain benefits when you pay for services on an as-needed basis for your business. You can spend more time innovating and inventing, which consequently reduces the complexity of procurement and enables your business to be fully elastic. ","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"805b488dc48f4591141569966cee0a89","text":"Enabling the full elasticity of business operations","correct":true},{"id":"48a2453a766bcd12a90a271271ca86a5","text":"Redirecting focus to innovation and invention","correct":true},{"id":"4657fb4ee914ab51c07ee5913b69cb48","text":"Reducing procurement complexity","correct":true},{"id":"8c0088e02946138166ef2d9e4bf9ab82","text":"Spending less money in the long term","correct":false},{"id":"d2c91d7ba7466b41bdbcd42e13db2ecb","text":"Spending more money in the long term","correct":false}]},{"id":"bccfe3b0-61d9-4680-81cc-45a78d8a722d","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following options are available for configuring a password policy for IAM users of an AWS account?","explanation":"The password policy options does not include the requirement of using at least one numerical character from 1 to 9; it is actually at least one numerical character from 0 to 9. Passwords can contain between 6 to 128 characters, so 12 to 64 characters is incorrect. The other three options listed are correct.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_credentials_passwords_account-policy.html?icmpid=docs_iam_console","title":"Setting an Account Password Policy for IAM Users"}],"answers":[{"id":"164affd52e9cf98d09976ffa798d82dd","text":"Allow users to change their passwords.","correct":true},{"id":"fcce064756de55a96a60925043d2feb0","text":"Use between 12 to 64 characters to form the password.","correct":false},{"id":"9fd02d6b80fbf23454be435b3ecbe598","text":"Use between 6 to 128 characters to form the password.","correct":true},{"id":"7115f92e53f08f3e583dcfde0a88161b","text":"Use at least one numerical character from 1 to 9.","correct":false},{"id":"454e4156bef76a1758de1fb18c771f5b","text":"Require that passwords contain at least one of the AWS-listed nonalphanumeric characters.","correct":true}]},{"id":"4nktsg9p-4zj3-dwhq-6y42-7tns3wptn2q7","domain":"tech","question":"You need a managed, low-cost relational database for your e-commerce store. Which of the following should you use?","explanation":"RDS is your best option: it's a low-cost, managed database solution. DynamoDB is a non-relational database, and not suitable for this scenario","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"About RDS"}],"answers":[{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"7fe48e833035175294ec48b4086b24e0","text":"AWS ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"58dbd4ac6f5e40d5300757915fa51606","text":"MySQL on EC2","correct":false},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":true}]},{"id":"86ed7d54-4495-435b-908a-b439c255c35d","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the five best practices does AWS Trusted Advisor use to eliminate unused, underutilized, and idle resources in your environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor ensures cost optimization of your AWS account by eliminating unused, underutilized, and idle resources, which include EC2 instances, load balancers, EBS volumes, and elastic IP addresses.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor Best Practice Checks"}],"answers":[{"id":"07d2fdfae089a6e085811b22437de261","text":"Service limits","correct":false},{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":false},{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":false},{"id":"45a75e44a713fdf94dbf1dbaa0749188","text":"Fault tolerance","correct":false},{"id":"a39ae09f8be4327fc176cfeb76a0e366","text":"Cost optimization","correct":true}]},{"id":"d29bb03a-1a55-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for? (Choose 3)","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services. Such services include Amazon VPC, which enables a customer to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud. This section is simply referred to as a virtual private cloud, or VPC. So, while AWS is responsible for the software (Amazon VPC), the customer is responsible for the virtual network created with that software (VPC), as well as whatever goes in it. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses) and security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"452be8d0a4b871d9b4ec8f7e323a17a2","text":"Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs)","correct":true},{"id":"1d7c6a62b7a045346e19186c911b38a1","text":"Amazon VPC Service","correct":false},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true}]},{"id":"e915ef52-2be6-4fba-8d62-b668f639c29a","domain":"billing","question":"To stay within the AWS Free Tier using Amazon EC2 for the first 12 months of having an AWS account, which of the following instance types should you use?","explanation":"One of the EC2 requirements for staying within the AWS Free Tier is using EC2 micro instances only. While the other instance types can be cheap, only t2.micro is eligibile for free tier usage","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"05c25e549fbb3f158f12a9945bff38ee","text":"t3.medium","correct":false},{"id":"cc114cafeb511c9cbe6666312f54a8de","text":"m5.medium","correct":false},{"id":"ab61127647912c159c3fc08e9a102efc","text":"t2.small","correct":false},{"id":"1d4f2c610dbeb44e7ba09fed19564c76","text":"t2.micro","correct":true}]},{"id":"561b98dd-beb4-4111-8cb8-b5609a124873","domain":"tech","question":"What benefits can CloudFront bring to your e-commerce website?","explanation":"CloudFront provides the ability to cache both static and dynamic content in 200 points of presence located around the world, ensuring quick response times can be had by customers when retrieving cached website content. This inclueds protections with AWS WAF and AWS Shield. No additional analytics will necessarily be available, nor is CloudFront a database solution","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/features/","title":"Amazon CloudFront Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"61c592ef1e234bfa1834570f2238d22f","text":"Advanced analytics into customer journeys","correct":false},{"id":"6c47d5971e79af6daf2b24070bd1e8ac","text":"Scalable managed database which integrates seamlessly with Lambda and EC2","correct":false},{"id":"bb42b85b5fcfff06d034f3102a1daa9e","text":"Lower latency for customers of your e-commerce website","correct":true},{"id":"3559eb841146fbbde9ede18594e319f1","text":"Protection against network and application layer attacks via WAF","correct":true},{"id":"286fe6e5d97e4ad18aac77cef2b5e28c","text":"Increased application availability","correct":true}]},{"id":"g7u8frqb-st05-cduw-gbms-boj1g5a4xb99","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below best describes DynamoDB?","explanation":"DynamoDB is a fast and flexible NoSQL database. NoSQL databases are non-relational, and have a dynamic structure, whereas SQL is relational and has a pre-defined structure. MySQL is a type of SQL database and Mongo is a type of NoSQL database, but neither of these are DynamoDB. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/dynamodb/","title":"DynamoDB"}],"answers":[{"id":"f311f0c1ec783313330a4fd83fbb6200","text":"DynamoDB is a NoSQL database","correct":true},{"id":"30baf17e85e225ed9bb718ded752d263","text":"DynamoDB is a an SQL database","correct":false},{"id":"482666cddcef688e890d4b901ebf8a32","text":"DynamoDB is a MySQL database","correct":false},{"id":"bbd2da8aa588d6741d84847621ad4503","text":"DynamoDB is a Mongo database","correct":false}]},{"id":"ab488ee0-acfc-4bf6-9b0a-832f6d99aeb3","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services is an example of Platform as a Service?","explanation":"Platform as a Service, or PaaS, enables the development, running, and management of applications on the cloud without the need to build and maintain an infrastructure. That is precisely what Elastic Beanstalk provides; itâ€™s the ability to quickly deploy and manage applications in the AWS Cloud without worrying about the infrastructure that runs those applications. Elastic Beanstalk is the only PaaS listed here.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticbeanstalk/","title":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk"}],"answers":[{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"bcf6eb183b7da148701bcc059a34675f","text":"AWS Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"270fcb785810d0206945029bb05f4e97","text":"Amazon S3","correct":false},{"id":"dee7ff8f7b10b9d388c7c561e9413b0d","text":"AWS Lambda","correct":false}]},{"id":"7e71f634-1fe3-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements are true of Amazon Redshift?","explanation":"Amazon Redshift is AWSâ€™s data warehouse service designed to scale up to petabytes of structured data. Using Redshift, you can create a data warehouse with a set of nodes, which is referred to as a 'cluster'.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/redshift/latest/mgmt/welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon Redshift?"}],"answers":[{"id":"c195feba1b6755cf70b23e85f649bea5","text":"It stores unstructured data.","correct":false},{"id":"cb8783f4a61d2d6ce45ab561107c68fe","text":"It is used to launch a set of nodes called a Redshift cluster.","correct":true},{"id":"1be4b9169c53e2842d313aa2e9fe2bc5","text":"It is a data warehouse service.","correct":true},{"id":"eae61ac52e73cabeaa3d471e1f2214dd","text":"It is designed for storing petabytes of data.","correct":true}]},{"id":"uvop23ho-2fn6-04p8-5luy-ybljxy0o0477","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following services helps you to deliver your content to your customers faster?","explanation":"Amazon CloudFront is a content delivery network that speeds the delivery of content to your users.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"About CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"34bc95906489c2d5c9583e3230cd48b2","text":"Elastic Block Store","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"02f85544eeded6ef1b6c40d62bcadddd","text":"Amazon Elastic File System","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false}]},{"id":"rqfj1uaw-51ci-mvl2-1djk-uzefaek5cehy","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following is correct?","explanation":"The number of Edge Locations is greater than the number of Availability Zones, which is greater than the number of Regions. Regions contain Availability Zones, therefore there will always be more AZs than Regions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"27268ba761c3ae0dbf9e4c8959f13e0f","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Regions > # of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"3782de3e5fc87f6e1a21193778c0d5bf","text":"# of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations > # of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"916cfd186ad7a451ebd785b35c738429","text":"# of Edge Locations > # of Availability Zones > # of Regions","correct":true},{"id":"07ebe9ccf5e5396c2f2c81de53d3829e","text":"# of Regions > # of Availability Zones > # of Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"cpv9q14j-4nnf-wb3n-urul-qo85pzcs4lot","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following best describes a Resource Group?","explanation":"A resource group is a collection of resources that share one or more tags (or portions of tags.)","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsconsolehelpdocs/latest/gsg/what-are-resource-groups.html","title":"What Are Resource Groups?"}],"answers":[{"id":"dabdc344de93e3ccb3d5245b1f871f94","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources of the same type (EC2, S3, etc.) that are deployed in the same Availability Zone.","correct":false},{"id":"85a53afa2201152c277b7a584e2933be","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources that are deployed in the same Availability Zone.","correct":false},{"id":"02853c1436655d9187bb9d61a5b2ce70","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources of the same type (EC2, S3, etc.) that share one or more tags or portions of tags.","correct":false},{"id":"7ff9ffa66bb042afad45110ef6296a1a","text":"A resource group is a collection of resources that share one or more tags (or portions of tags.)","correct":true}]},{"id":"f119625a-2f3b-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your Project Manager needs to know the daily spend of the companyâ€™s AWS account over the last 60 days to consider creating and implementing cost-effective measures. What should you do?","explanation":"Cost Explorer provides a trio of preconfigured views designed to quickly get you to common spends in your AWS environment. For viewing the daily spend over the last 60 days, your Project Manager needs to click the 'Daily Spend View' link. AWS Budgets is for generating automatic alerts when your AWS costs or usage exceed, or are forecasted to exceed, the thresholds you set; it is not for tracking your spend.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-what-is.html","title":"What Is AWS Billing and Cost Management?"}],"answers":[{"id":"ae4dff5b9f90f7f36261f1743d9c6eb1","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Linked Account View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"3061bd4594121d528b00ebc0b3cabd8b","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Service View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"224e965acad73b5fc7fd31b503e947db","text":"Direct him to Daily Spend View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":true},{"id":"e3963c15d2d033b249d8f75f4b7c05ff","text":"Direct him to AWS Budgets.","correct":false}]},{"id":"8ae68d9e-7bf8-41c2-996a-a01fb1bf966a","domain":"billing","question":"Which tool can help you to compare the cost of hosting resources in AWS vs the cost of hosting in a traditional data centre?","explanation":"The TCO calculators allow you to estimate the cost savings when using AWS and provide a detailed set of reports.  Pricing Calculator can be used to estimate potential AWS spend, and AWS Budgets & Billing Alarms can help keep spend under control by alerting you when you breach a threshold.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","title":"AWS TCO Calculator"}],"answers":[{"id":"1a98a10ad310a9ed66414dd3acb48e72","text":"AWS Pricing Calculator","correct":false},{"id":"e84e1dd83afcda636af8a6ae32a58cef","text":"AWS TCO Calculator","correct":true},{"id":"6b6f2097ec6555c2e09b7ed23571b3c5","text":"AWS Billing Alarms","correct":false},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false}]},{"id":"86d0ccb9-ab67-4952-a7ea-0fea12fc6c1f","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to data security in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which includes security. The customer is responsible for who can access the data itself.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"7a0bc438686e10d5e1ab102d0dc0e4a9","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":false},{"id":"9f02eb6c8050b89db31831403951787b","text":"The customer is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":true},{"id":"2844802845f801aded529f1d22c63d82","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":true},{"id":"599dca975551e5a41106ce454a46e4e0","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":true},{"id":"6e8271456f0c471167caae0d75aab487","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":false},{"id":"0ed894aaf38bd44ba33d1612854617d0","text":"AWS is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":false}]},{"id":"7a194fa6-5966-4548-9b32-ac602a517ac8","domain":"concepts","question":"With AWS services, you can use as many resources as you need, as well as use them when you need them. Which of the following terms can be applied to this concept?","explanation":"Working in a traditional infrastructure environment means that you have to deal with fixed resources, which is comparatively costly and labor-intensive. By contrast, AWS services are much more convenient; the services provide the ability to use as many resources as you need and dispose of them when you no longer need them. Thatâ€™s why such resources are both temporary and disposable.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"83ec702ebd8e13f87318dba136356773","text":"Dedicated resources","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"e035a6f9ed7c8c3c99e48b95e32cc364","text":"Fixed resources","correct":false},{"id":"5936fc4450b6f3f75cc6fe08d2890b77","text":"Temporary resources","correct":true}]},{"id":"32c7f1bb-425d-4d33-b870-b88f89ef9f08","domain":"security","question":"An oil and gas utility company which is highly regulated must create a cloud governance scheme. The company is organized into multiple autonomous departments which will all be using AWS resources. These departments each sponsor independent projects that are reviewed by regulatory boards for the approval of customer price increases. The code and infrastructure for each project has production, development, and testing environments. Which of the following account strategies will maximize security and operational efficiency for the company?","explanation":"A multi-layered account structure will work best for this company, leveraging AWS Organizations to establish Organizational Units for each department, and separate production, development, and testing environments. While there is no physical AWS account at the department level, Service Control Policies can be applied at the Organizational Unit level, and billing can be reported separately for each department. An account for each department, in which the department combines dev/test/and prod, or a single account for the company hosting all workloads together will NOT provide for segregation of production, development, and testing environments at the account level. Multiple standalone accounts for each department and environment would compromise operational efficiency in managing environments across departments as there is no overarching AWS Organization to manage all the accounts centrally.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/Security/AWS_Security_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"AWS Security Best Practices"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/organizations/","title":"AWS Organizations"}],"answers":[{"id":"e4be6081f1a5dc1cc67c1a4633121580","text":"Create an Organization Unit structure in AWS Organizations with separate underlying accounts for production, development, and testing environments","correct":true},{"id":"bb38e2c475c21f60a71674d4dd27ff93","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for each autonomous department within the company","correct":false},{"id":"6773420477c1653d8837f13bfa8ec24d","text":"Create a single AWS account for centralized security management","correct":false},{"id":"281f961ca6e4d83f6570979548ba64e2","text":"Create multiple AWS accounts, one for the production environment, one for the development environment, and one for the testing environment for all departments","correct":false}]},{"id":"b7755a84-2ede-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services fall under the Migration and Transfer category?","explanation":"Database Migration Service is for migrating databases to AWS, and Snowball is for using devices to transfer large amounts of data in and out of the AWS Cloud. So, both services are Migration and Transfer services. Redshift is Amazonâ€™s data warehouse solution, and ElastiCache is an in-memory data store; both are database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"e30020a3e07c8d84a925df2ca76a2af5","text":"AWS Database Migration Service","correct":true},{"id":"f7415e33f972c03abd4f3fed36748f7a","text":"Amazon Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"770b120ec487568871cc9ab64475af46","text":"Amazon ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"c2d838ea2b9043be2161255da328dc60","text":"AWS Snowball","correct":true}]},{"id":"zlyf2s8s-kula-sxtl-s07a-i3uh455n1hnu","domain":"security","question":"Which credentials can you use to access the AWS Management console?","explanation":"You use a username and password to log into the AWS console, although Access key and Secret Access key can be used to access some APIs programmatically","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"The AWS Management Console"}],"answers":[{"id":"4dd4dfb52929ef230415ada1a4169dc1","text":"Your Security Token","correct":false},{"id":"2a7454c71a60c06ab2189283f1788e09","text":"Your Secret Access key","correct":false},{"id":"be677306ceb7d966e7a06ee1bf387acf","text":"Your Access key","correct":false},{"id":"afc76c6d8222878e0449abb2ea16838f","text":"Your Username and Password","correct":true}]},{"id":"su6exaen-uvfq-awbs-r1m3-y06rtjhsbaw6","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services can help you assess the fault-tolerance of your AWS environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor can help you assess the fault-tolerance of your AWS environment. AWS Inspector can help you assess your security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"About Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false}]},{"id":"7b242f9e-5541-40b9-94c3-ff760252f026","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following scenarios are examples of scaling an IT architecture vertically?","explanation":"To scale vertically is to increase the specifications of a single AWS resource as needed. For example, resizing EC2 or RDS instances for more CPU, memory, or network capabilities is scaling vertically. Adding more EC2 or RDS instances, on the other hand, is scaling horizontally because it involves the increase in the number of resources, rather than the increase in each resourceâ€™s capabilities.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"4fd553484e87f00281d8e2d07df1c3ac","text":"Resizing an EC2 instance type from a1.medium to a1.xlarge for more CPU and memory power","correct":true},{"id":"d2ed8876ad5d876850ebcde76e28bd9f","text":"Adding two more EC2 instances","correct":false},{"id":"f9de222cea376a61a621e215c4daf0dc","text":"Resizing an RDS instance type from db.r5.large to db.r5.2xlarge","correct":true},{"id":"67c96e88044c732523807882de714af3","text":"Adding two more RDS instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"yvxo9l3i-wh4o-2dqm-3mnu-snzqe8qbcn6w","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes an AWS Region?","explanation":"A Region is a distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography. Regions are a key concept in AWS' Global Infrastructure - each is made up of one or more isolated (within that region) Availability Zones. There are often multiple AWS Regions on each continent, such as North America","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"8c91beabafc69d771d60455febdc0927","text":"A console that gives you a quick, global picture of your cloud computing environment.","correct":false},{"id":"cd212d0c12772fef24104f0585e29933","text":"A collection of data centres that are spread evenly around a specific continent.","correct":false},{"id":"02994d9c387a384eeaa6efd09a6dd102","text":"A distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography.","correct":true},{"id":"1230f90d0fb76db29194467e14f8e099","text":"A collection of databases that can only be accessed from a specific geographic region.","correct":false}]},{"id":"1ad299fd-63d9-4a60-9949-d88b086002cf","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE when running a database in an EC2 Instance?","explanation":"In this case - as the database is being run in an EC2 instance, all aspects of database updates and access is the responsibility of the customer. Similarly as it is and EC2 instance, the customer is responsible for OS patching. Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which in this case is the EC2 instance - anything to do with the instance itself is the responsibility of the customer ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"52f2eff0e91b46fe3007ca238393c185","text":"The customer is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"42d5fd24fef6883fb899e3afd050b5a5","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":true},{"id":"199f4eaff96b0da13d07770ee0ff2ab4","text":"AWS is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":false},{"id":"9f9f41256e31feca524f1209e25d70fa","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the database software","correct":true},{"id":"0d6e04dd939a298f20dd927b2a10aa7c","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":false},{"id":"c7098373cbee0fc9617269a6d3765dd4","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the database software","correct":false}]},{"id":"84d8ac20-2fb5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Once you exceed a usage percentage of Free Tier limits for any service, AWS will automatically send you an email notification. What is that percentage?","explanation":"If you exceed 85% of Free Tier usage, AWS will automatically send you an email to notify you. This is to alert you to help with staying within the Free Tier limits; otherwise, you may incur charges.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html","title":"Tracking Your Free Tier Usage"}],"answers":[{"id":"1c383cd30b7c298ab50293adfecb7b18","text":"35","correct":false},{"id":"c0c7c76d30bd3dcaefc96f40275bdc0a","text":"50","correct":false},{"id":"3ef815416f775098fe977004015c6193","text":"85","correct":true},{"id":"d09bf41544a3365a46c9077ebb5e35c3","text":"75","correct":false}]},{"id":"48590e18-0af6-4579-8b7e-3e6d32dfdc94","domain":"billing","question":"What EC2 pricing model enables bidding at whatever price is desired for instance capacity, thereby making it ideal for flexibility with application start and end times?","explanation":"While On Demand allows a fixed rate payment by the hour or second with no commitment and Reserved provides a capacity reservation, it is the Spot EC2 pricing model that enables bidding on the desired price for instance capacity. By contrast with the other pricing models, Dedicated Hosts consists of an actual physical EC2 server.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"6c9d6b8aea6f3d16847bdebe05878a2d","text":"Spot","correct":true},{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":false},{"id":"244492cdce9dce0555c52ebe1182e0a3","text":"On Demand","correct":false},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":false}]},{"id":"zejpj051-p0tv-b1pt-hvqk-i5pz24d88v68","domain":"tech","question":"Which AWS service allows you to run code without having to worry about provisioning any underlying resources (such as virtual machines, databases etc.)","explanation":"Lambda is the AWS Function-as-a-Service (FaaS) offering that lets you run code without provisioning or managing servers. Elastic Container Service (ECS) uses containers, but still requires management of the underlying servers to some extent. EC2 uses traditional servers, and does require all the other resources to be provisioned and setup. DynamoDB is specifically used for storing information in non-relational databases, and is unable to run code.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true}]},{"id":"8af9065f-42ab-4684-937d-6ff9a21fce3a","domain":"tech","question":"You visit a clients site and get called into a corridor discussion. You are asked to describe the new (2019) URL structure for objects in S3.  Which of these do you use as a description.","explanation":"AWS has updated the URL format for objects in S3 in order to partition the name space.  This will introduce more consistency, but be aware that there are still multiple variation depending on feature and location.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-path-deprecation-plan-the-rest-of-the-story/","title":"New S3 path format"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/rande.html#s3_region","title":"S3 Regional Endpoints"}],"answers":[{"id":"f2a5230ac12d8264aebebe8dfedd74a5","text":" http, then the bucket name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"db8e7027e46c062db1befedc330f0884","text":" https, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then dot, then the bucket name, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"9b571c57c4bcb1635a0422505e741908","text":" https, then the bucket name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":true},{"id":"ab8096a72368e95dc6011f1758564494","text":" https, then the object name, then slash, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then bucket the name","correct":false},{"id":"ae3cbeae173c8a519b7847f15141def6","text":" https, then the bucket name, then slash, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"e9fd54ece61badbfe41eb84932fcb635","text":" http, then the object name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then dot, then bucket the name","correct":false},{"id":"a91ee87d632a84e3d44d1f44d80dc38e","text":" https, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the bucket name, then slash, then the object name","correct":false}]},{"id":"04uew9ya-7pbn-ugmi-3vzh-1erxijop26v7","domain":"billing","question":"You are an AWS Enterprise customer with questions about billing and your overall AWS account. Which of the following AWS support personnel should you contact?","explanation":"For AWS Enterprise customers, the AWS Concierge is a resource dedicated to answering billing and account questions.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/features/","title":"AWS Support Features"}],"answers":[{"id":"aebccaafe1827e1ed91b1d9a27dac4a8","text":"AWS Technical Account Manager","correct":false},{"id":"bac90b5cd782c7dc092efa042af32e5c","text":"AWS Concierge","correct":true},{"id":"0037cad42801741c9acb59d7d7ba9a5f","text":"AWS Billing and Accounts","correct":false},{"id":"26e8220e8fac28d2a1a9a18ca81aabd7","text":"AWS Support","correct":false}]},{"id":"69916ab3-c78a-4abd-86a8-5dc73e90916a","domain":"tech","question":"Your manager approaches you this morning to tell you there has been a surprise audit announced by the internal audit team for all of your company's AWS Accounts. Which service would you use to provide the necessary information to the audit team?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail is a service that enables governance, compliance, operational and risk auditing of your AWS account.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"1aa2d5ab75afef6fa4ccd1e3b22174d4","text":"QuickSight","correct":false},{"id":"9deb03cd21d41a691cdc24bfaab2820c","text":"Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":true}]},{"id":"5d7bea17-63ec-412b-bb14-bd0a1f5c4683","domain":"concepts","question":"If you have a new application and you are not sure about future demand, which of the below characteristics of cloud make cloud an ideal place to host it?","explanation":"No upfront & Pay as you go mean that you do not need an initial outlay of capital for resources to build in cloud, and only need to pay for what you use going forward. These combined with the ability to consume more resources when needed (Scalability) mean that cloud is a great way to host applications that have dynamic requirements. No Single Points of Failure and High Availability should be included in any design, but are not intrinsic to cloud. Similarly, although Performance Efficiency is key, this comes down to you application and it's design, and is not a characteristic of the cloud. ","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"e95a95951d99b5f038c688bf69bd5a01","text":"Pay as you go","correct":true},{"id":"9043a5d84d85473bd60ab9b11f10b04b","text":"No single point of failure","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"5c751a74a73417fb82a2cc45c4edc2cb","text":"No upfront","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"bc368b371822f4e7df28c5768582dde8","text":"Performance Efficiency","correct":false}]},{"id":"cliqnjyx-pd1z-74c0-p0h5-gl8ufv76fo42","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are valid EC2 pricing options?","explanation":"On-Demand, where you pay for the resources you have used at the end of the billing period, and Reserved, were you commit to paying a certain amount every billing period for a length of time no matter if you used them or not, are the valid EC2 pricing options.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"4cc6684df7b4a92b1dec6fce3264fac8","text":"Global","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true}]},{"id":"o8aqfsp4-kk6k-gyj7-frq7-4bpn7iv5zqm8","domain":"concepts","question":"You have a mission-critical application which must be globally available at all times. Which deployment strategy should you follow?","explanation":"A Multi-Region deployment will best ensure global availability. While it can be the most expensive, and complex to configure, Multi-Regional architectures will ensure that even if all Availability Zones in a single region fail due to a catastrophic event, your data will remain accessible.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"86b2c5243e03e210528f020bad4efdb9","text":"Multi-VPC in two AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"ec206762c0bea997a5b0f91783cce54f","text":"Multi-Availability Zone","correct":false},{"id":"e4ec2833a31f482abfdb31691f0351dc","text":"Multi-Region","correct":true},{"id":"91d7ff212b9bda483701aeb4209ae5ec","text":"Deploy to all Availability Zones in your home region.","correct":false}]},{"id":"kftbhvi5-gvt3-4gao-hmti-h8ln0k10oi0l","domain":"tech","question":"The Solutions Architect leading your project tells you the application your team is working on requires a managed NoSQL database. Which of the following AWS services best fits that description?","explanation":"DynamoDB is AWS' managed NoSQL database.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/dynamodb/","title":"About DynamoDB"}],"answers":[{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false},{"id":"50848259480914860b338e7baf94c29a","text":"ElastiCache","correct":false},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":true}]},{"id":"55632ec1-3922-4d04-80c0-ff9b5b21c2d2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are AWS EC2 reserved pricing types?","explanation":"Reserved instances have three main pricing models, Standard, Convertible and Scheduled. Each model is targeted with a specific use case and benefits from its own level of discounted price","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"c9e63a71aa24afcde5e964d2530e2524","text":"Compute Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"bd1ad3385adf098b2e87d2bb75d87e39","text":"Scalable Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"e507a844b940fd588a1cbb5bb46fd4fe","text":"Standard Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"c81edad1f6d23ac52025cde1cf22ba7b","text":"Scheduled Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"fe501a6493589e0d87e90fd0b4361e6f","text":"Convertable Reserved Instances","correct":true}]},{"id":"80c462fa-2fa6-11ea-aec2-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support plans provide access to online self-paced labs for training staff?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan provides access to online self-paced labs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false}]},{"id":"41fd3ae6-76b4-4f5f-8ee6-4f5688f969dc","domain":"tech","question":"You want to use an AWS service that enables you to notify select Tech Support members in your company (via email) of any cloud-related issues to attend to. Which of the following services will accomplish that?","explanation":"With Simple Notification Service, or Amazon SNS, you can create and appropriately name a topic to which you publish your messages. Then the select Tech Support members can be subscribed to that topic to receive these messages as email notifications.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/sns/","title":"Amazon SNS"}],"answers":[{"id":"142db9d2b615fcb75a6dd2e4a2a9eb2a","text":"Simple Queue Service","correct":false},{"id":"1f4072738a4917bea022b11256fb46a4","text":"Simple Workflow Service","correct":false},{"id":"7ba6eb634dd2e14688216874c0948a82","text":"Simple Notification Service","correct":true},{"id":"e99b5e1a7bf908cbe637b87720eb88c2","text":"Simple Email Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true},{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false},{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false}]},{"id":"955c3d5e-7bce-4502-a765-a1b7883e6b42","domain":"billing","question":"Why would you use Tags in AWS?","explanation":"A tag is a label that you or AWS assigns to an AWS resource. You can use tags to organize your resources, and cost allocation tags to track your AWS costs on a detailed level.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"2a83d3966af703cdd10973b715644342","text":"To store code","correct":false},{"id":"8fa9b4921f616acb2d005a4fb25ea9e2","text":"To organize your resources","correct":true},{"id":"3785763b04891a512dcbd1f190ddde7a","text":"To store passwords for your servers","correct":false},{"id":"881e2086647235f606ee190833b2b149","text":"For a No-SQL data store","correct":false}]},{"id":"2df4774c-2e69-4156-96c5-b1efbfba754f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. This means there will always be more AZs than Regions. Edge locations are separate from AZs and Regions, and there are more Edge Locations than Regions and Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"f35fa3c5e765907efd6efa66bc1741c3","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Regions","correct":false},{"id":"f4b49cc5b3d286cd78cac99f03cecce3","text":"There are more Regions than Availability zones","correct":false},{"id":"26c658a3c4aee0122f0178a65f0ea80b","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Regions","correct":true},{"id":"29030db1d3f86fea8d8779a9c964c207","text":"There are more Availability Zones than Edge locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"cfea2363-9af8-4536-b812-8ea53c44b11b","domain":"security","question":"You just had a Data Analyst join the company, and you have been tasked with creating a new IAM user accordingly. Although the user has received all the necessary credentials, she realized that she cannot perform any Amazon RDS actions on the Clients table. Which of the following are possible solutions to this issue?","explanation":"By default, an IAM user canâ€™t access anything in the AWS account. So, the inability to perform the RDS actions on the Clients table is not a technical or password issue. To grant the permission to do so, you would need to create an identity-based policy. However, if there is a group in the account with the permission policy that will grant such access, you can add the user to that group instead.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_access-management.html","title":"Overview of Access Management: Permissions and Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"1971cb80efb016ad4254e3847a847434","text":"Supply the password necessary to log into the AWS console.","correct":false},{"id":"2f96bead1d7909e64836767c4e098acd","text":"Create an identity-based policy.","correct":true},{"id":"f46d75eb223838121ca6bec9ca08eaaa","text":"Create a ticket for the Help Desk to resolve the issue.","correct":false},{"id":"7731c1bfd28c89eee71012d973fa5407","text":"Double-check the credentials you sent to the user.","correct":false},{"id":"94412f8679d11dc0613f571ca4fba16b","text":"Add the user to the group that has the necessary permissions policy.","correct":true}]},{"id":"eaf197bf-a9f1-4611-90be-dbcf7364c74a","domain":"concepts","question":"You have an application load balancer for routing traffic from developers to the EC2 instance that contains a web application being put into operation. To prepare for the application going live for public use, you add an Auto Scaling Group and a second application load balancer to route web traffic from customers to the EC2 instance. The addition is an example of which of the following:","explanation":"This is an example of scalability, which means that systems are expected to grow over time with no drop in performance. ","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"820b8f74ad843d1574106ec4cadfc07e","text":"Reliability","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"2166e76dc88d642260416a536b06a412","text":"Durability","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true}]},{"id":"ybx4uf1a-l9y3-aucn-tt1m-ku92d3hu5y5v","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are configuratble components of IAM?","explanation":"Users, Groups, Roles, and Permissions are integral to IAM. Authentication and Authorization are functions that IAM provides, but not actual components of it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/getting-started/","title":"IAM - Getting Started"}],"answers":[{"id":"3948d67c633d9035eaf2216ba0e1b2dc","text":"Authenticator","correct":false},{"id":"2999b7d01e6b02e94fc22c79b978d3b0","text":"Access controls","correct":false},{"id":"a5cd3ed116608dac017f14c046ea56bf","text":"Roles","correct":true},{"id":"f9aae5fda8d810a29f12d1e61b4ab25f","text":"Users","correct":true},{"id":"18ade94f5fe966167a6645362290cdcb","text":"Authorizer","correct":false},{"id":"d08ccf52b4cdd08e41cfb99ec42e0b29","text":"Permissions","correct":true},{"id":"a37ede293936e29279ed543129451ec3","text":"Groups","correct":true}]},{"id":"cckhl0ep-pmhf-g8be-yplb-dzr17jgnk6mn","domain":"security","question":"Where is the best place to store your Root User Access Key so that your application can use it to make requests to AWS?","explanation":"It is not recommended to use Root User account or access keys for any reason as these grant full unrestricted access to the entire account. Recommended practice is to follow the concept of \"Least Privilege\" and create am IAM user or role with just enough access to do what is needed and nothing more, and use those keys as required","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws-access-keys-best-practices.html","title":"Best Practices for Managing AWS Access Keys"}],"answers":[{"id":"73532a5c24d7b4c1df276690bbaedfff","text":"In the .aws file in you application","correct":false},{"id":"503d72b0254a8561511b71a95f8eb8a7","text":"It should be configured as a parameter and held in the Key Management Store (KMS)","correct":false},{"id":"9feb4a526584eae16c38880b7813f48c","text":"It needs to be coded directly into your application","correct":false},{"id":"2330278fe444dd9a6196cb146c97de7e","text":"Nowhere - you should not use the Root User access keys for this","correct":true}]},{"id":"19ddf237-f79d-4d25-b0ae-81419166300b","domain":"security","question":"Enabling Amazon GuardDuty automatically grants this service the permission to analyze which of the following data sources?","explanation":"Amazon GuardDuty monitors the security of your AWS environment by analyzing and processing three data sources, which are VPC Flow Logs, AWS CloudTrail event logs, and DNS logs.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/guardduty/latest/ug/what-is-guardduty.html","title":"What is GuardDuty?"}],"answers":[{"id":"da9b46af667cf2279d002b955813bb34","text":"AWS CloudTrail logs","correct":true},{"id":"8db8c2b0bbd0ff71d1d15bb32f69e3b8","text":"VPC Flow Logs","correct":true},{"id":"a70a14359eb44629c70e41470e05570f","text":"DNS query logs","correct":true},{"id":"6b7cef11406f2fff58dcc619a2b7e482","text":"Amazon S3 buckets","correct":false}]},{"id":"ai3ijdez-wtig-dn7p-p04b-jb32lm26m7cb","domain":"tech","question":"In order to comply with regulatory mandates, some of your data needs to be retained in perpetuity. Which of the following AWS storage services offers low-cost, long-term data archival?","explanation":"Glacier is your best choice for deeply-discounted, long-term object archival - as long as the data does not need to be available and online at a moment's notice.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/","title":"About Glacier"}],"answers":[{"id":"f332127ba5ee3389e4c5cff45ac9a518","text":"EFS","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"4def2a084469f97f6372bfaf0823941b","text":"Glacier","correct":true},{"id":"f52a9d91766886fb3a524dd06d1581cb","text":"Redshift","correct":false}]},{"id":"485886ee-d768-43eb-bf66-99dbf6ca890f","domain":"tech","question":"When might Auto Scaling be used?","explanation":"Auto Scaling monitors your applications and automatically adjusts capacity to maintain steady, predictable performance at the lowest possible cost.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"AWS Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"81a09fc79a5b8e06c0ba313f0c38b98f","text":"To provision resources that can be adjusted once per 24 hour period","correct":false},{"id":"653f92bb6e8a7e984815d88099db9ab2","text":"To control provisioning of S3 bucket capacity","correct":false},{"id":"294a68b8b2e864aff39edf8b7b5ae662","text":"Where predictable workload patterns exist","correct":false},{"id":"4576fb5ff37cef52dcd4b0610521a97c","text":"When you require scalable capacity to maintain service levels in your environment","correct":true}]},{"id":"mlqp7x88-xfgl-3xkm-trto-wx59uhf7dox6","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below allows you to restrict access to individual objects in an S3 bucket? ","explanation":"Access Control Lists let you control access to individual objects within an S3 bucket, whereas Bucket Policies allow you to control access to entire buckets. In relation to S3, Bucket Control Lists and Access Policies do not exist as configuration items.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/using-iam-policies.html","title":"About S3 Bucket Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"7cfde5ee620a2532233ca18a68fd35ba","text":"Bucket Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":true},{"id":"64d03326bddfa39f7ae9a129e8b731c6","text":"Bucket Access Lists","correct":false},{"id":"8eaf761b0344c54cfcf063cb006e4ad1","text":"Access Policies","correct":false}]},{"id":"pjzmsz8b-2lx2-8zb8-wauh-od1x4h0ja4pd","domain":"tech","question":"A new System Administrator has started with your organisation and requires a user account so that they can manage you AWS resources. You have AWS resources in multiple regions - what needs to be done to allow the new starter access to manage resources in the regions you operate in?","explanation":"Any answer that suggest a role is incorrect as roles by themselves will not let a user log in. The correct approach is to create an IAM user - and as IAM is a global service - configuration in IAM applies globally, not just regionally, only a single IAM user account is required.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction.html","title":"What is IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"98cddae0b6f5dfe1792d38678a9851a0","text":"Create an IAM role in each region that you have resources in - this will enable access in per region","correct":false},{"id":"15ed84de219d4333fe7069904bec4dbc","text":"Create an IAM user account in each region that you have resources in - this will enable access in per region","correct":false},{"id":"f854b98dd0b3ff05864e11c45979706b","text":"Create a single IAM user account - this will enable access in all regions","correct":true},{"id":"2effe9ac093a8dcafdd02f3e97c1244e","text":"Create a single IAM role - this will enable access in all regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true},{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false},{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true},{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false}]},{"id":"7gpfi6zh-od3t-hgmy-7puh-d955spmckv2u","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound cloud design?","explanation":"Build your systems to be scalable, use disposable resources, reduce infrastructure to code, and, please, assume EVERYTHING will fail sooner or later. Servers should be treated like cattle, where the exist to serve a function, and for a generally limited period of time, as opposed to pets which are kept and cared for over very long periods of time. There is no reason to limit the number of 3rd party services, if it makes the most sense in the case of the design at hand. Tightly-coupled components result in hard dependencies between different services, and usually lead to issues with either an applications health, or its scalability.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"31ae780d15d60c68f6689a039e6f3802","text":"Assume *everything* will fail.","correct":true},{"id":"df89f307a97b6ecf5647735dcd89f7c8","text":"Limit the number of 3rd-party services.","correct":false},{"id":"9cb4d987bd4d50912c60823480c86972","text":"Treat your servers like pets, not cattle.","correct":false},{"id":"c4feabf8a0fd67917d77220d3b036291","text":"Tightly-coupled components","correct":false},{"id":"af41549605744cf23f27cbc14458bf82","text":"Infrastructure as code","correct":true}]},{"id":"a6f49f26-0fbc-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for Amazon RDS?","explanation":"You can pay for Amazon RDS using either On-Demand or Reserved instance pricing.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"bda9eb7fcdccf237f87fb190ee3b4275","text":"Dedicated Server","correct":false},{"id":"e26ff95de7b422fa8d7999578d2becc3","text":"On-Demand","correct":true},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"6c9d6b8aea6f3d16847bdebe05878a2d","text":"Spot","correct":false}]},{"id":"n7rouwfc-9cnc-mywz-rj44-v3c021ws4ry3","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following acts like built-in firewalls per instance for your virtual servers?","explanation":"Security Groups act like built-in firewalls for your virtual servers - the rules you create define what is allowed to talk to your instances and how. Although Network Access Control Lists can be used to block or deny traffic, these operate at the subnet level - covering all instances in the subnet with the same ruleset, not per-instance as the question specifies. Route tables tell traffic where it should go next to reach its destination, and an Availability Zone is a collection of datacentres - which isn't relevant in this question. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-network-security.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Security Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":true},{"id":"8f36276b8cef5979b167a77e143d894e","text":"Route Tables","correct":false},{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":false}]},{"id":"f81195c4-7959-4925-a41d-e50f901cccad","domain":"tech","question":"Your System Administration team lead wants you to subscribe to the RSS feed to be notified of any interruptions to the EC2 service in the N. California and Ohio Regions. Which of the following will enable you to do that?","explanation":"Service Health Dashboard displays the general status of AWS services, such as EC2, and it enables RSS subscription. The Personal Health Dashboard does provide information about the services you're using, but it does not give you the ability to subscribe to RSS feeds.","links":[{"url":"https://status.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Service Health Dashboard"}],"answers":[{"id":"cf4db9f312542c8284a6ccdefcd98544","text":"Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"087edf830b5f3b392ebaef37ba8550f7","text":"EC2 Health Dashboard","correct":false},{"id":"5b60dd28958c0d6d59a455cc074e4322","text":"Service Health Dashboard","correct":true},{"id":"8e75b153e61c22a8ea4e14aadc7cb4ee","text":"Systems Manager","correct":false}]},{"id":"150e71c2-9b46-4a48-bed4-ef89f73570ae","domain":"tech","question":"Although you know that your Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS) volumes are designed to be highly reliable, you want to further mitigate the possibility of a failure. Which of the following should you do?","explanation":"Backup of the EBS volumes can be created by taking point-in-time snapshots. These components are stored in S3. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/EBSSnapshots.html","title":"Amazon EBS Snapshots"},{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-building-fault-tolerant-applications.pdf?did=wp_card&trk=wp_card","title":"Fault-Tolerant Components on AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"2f63e74501f200b9859c7b5976101e79","text":"Make copies of the EBS volumes and store them in Amazon S3.","correct":false},{"id":"44023459578ef9dc57780fc55ee56f7d","text":"Take snapshots of the EBS volumes.","correct":true},{"id":"a2a7a68497095df080fb01033b2aea46","text":"Create backups of the EBS volumes in Amazon RDS.","correct":false},{"id":"e2f843acc6781a153857118f92da89f4","text":"Mitigating the possibility of a failure is not necessary.","correct":false}]},{"id":"smnrxkfv-dk56-snvh-i93e-or0vfomvccbz","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are characteristics of cloud computing?","explanation":"The on-demand delivery via the internet of services with pay-as-you-go pricing characterizes cloud computing. Services incurred from a cloud services provider are operating expenses, not capital expenses. Capital Expenditure (CAPEX) is less common with the cloud, in favour of Operational Expenditure (OPEX). Skills and training for personnel are required to leverage Cloud Computing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"481f1c72f1007c1ac8e4a484b47af4f2","text":"Cloud charges are Capital Expenditures.","correct":false},{"id":"dcfe379beaf88dbe9d59e7fcecf6f98a","text":"Services are delivered via the Internet.","correct":true},{"id":"ebc744edbd870e96fe9e680b407ad053","text":"On-demand delivery","correct":true},{"id":"9b670633c5238ca5a17dd651c3a63662","text":"No extra skills or training are required.","correct":false},{"id":"2b34d3fef0b313e0047a2557d9842378","text":"Pay-as-you-go pricing","correct":true}]},{"id":"9n50o6rz-03s4-bpbd-i7dy-36qby4h0ka5x","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for when running an RDS database on AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance), as well as making sure the underlying OS and application is up to date. You as the user are responsible for keeping your data secure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"0266c79a8678f6881cc2857043b46509","text":"Controlling access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"57b862a3c428d3330f8c03216acd2c16","text":"Controlling access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"2b6b76aaf679124f3da7b20c5df23923","text":"Updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"8782b4a6bdea28cea082df1413a7f818","text":"Controlling access to the compute hardware","correct":false},{"id":"86da12905838c932b65844a3fa01aa08","text":"Updating the operating system","correct":false}]},{"id":"1978e26b-04e4-45ca-8a47-205e50d96c7f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are seperate from Regions and AZs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"22d0cb7092012aea1123fcbd58c6519c","text":"Data Centres contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"988326895b235b7a5f2b7eea1a9838f5","text":"Regions contain Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"cd6f4614de9281b97b511a1f3f534e8c","text":"Edge Locations contain Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"23b72701776466936b717d47eb3be164","text":"Availability Zones contain Data Centres","correct":true}]},{"id":"918c058b-8c3d-4858-aa1b-de986b3379af","domain":"security","question":"Which following statement is true of newly created security groups with their default rules?","explanation":"By default, new security groups start with only an outbound rule to allow all traffic to leave the instances. You must add rules to enable any inbound traffic.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/VPC_SecurityGroups.html","title":"Security Groups for Your VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"d00cd55aa36c87aedb13b4c0829aa462","text":"New security groups block both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"d21ab4dffc222de4dfe6fddddca20b1f","text":"New security groups allow both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"66152806bd7636ccc1a33303917cdddd","text":"New security groups allow only outbound traffic and block all incoming traffic.","correct":true},{"id":"8fbe4c39dc7d852a0b8aaa5b889b1ff1","text":"New security groups block outbound traffic and allow all incoming traffic.","correct":false}]},{"id":"caa31392-2fbc-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following engines are classified as relational databases on AWS?","explanation":"Amazon Aurora, Microsoft SQL Server, and MariaDB are three types of RDS engines on AWS. By contrast, DynamoDB is Amazonâ€™s nonrelational database solution.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"Amazon Relational Database Service (RDS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"78898e52fcbdc5337204a384f2456d4f","text":"Microsoft SQL Server","correct":true},{"id":"7f9733e208088b1ce6df3d4be1765396","text":"MariaDB","correct":true},{"id":"69670a9d53817d1ec89e685997343ce2","text":"Amazon Aurora","correct":true}]},{"id":"q9rl4dzm-8wyq-y23f-41wx-15rhrz976akb","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are a collection of datacentres within a specific region?","explanation":"Availability Zones are a collection of datacentres within a specific region.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"1fb6aae6611aa5001c41c1e356609c41","text":"Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false}]},{"id":"9da21f94-7d9e-4bcf-8c7c-fc97b0634977","domain":"security","question":"Your company has updated its security policies to include cloud workloads as well as those running on-premises. Your manager would like a report of which technologies will require configuration changes. Which of the following will not be included in the report because they are the responsibility of AWS?","explanation":"In the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, AWS in responsible for managing host operating systems. Users are responsible for managing guest operating systems, as well as Security Group Firewalls, Amazon Aurora data encryption, and S3 access control lists.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"63c21f07ff59add0f7e474ef5ec57c2e","text":"Security Group firewalls","correct":false},{"id":"8061595e3a5f2fb2195dd627dd35f5d2","text":"Host operating systems","correct":true},{"id":"64f8358ae4360eddd993acde2d19789c","text":"Amazon Aurora data encryption","correct":false},{"id":"331bd4e2a8ab147e5a6a47e5b9c40d65","text":"S3 Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"wdbn1na1-vwoh-03r9-ogc9-1ol20ezabw11","domain":"tech","question":"You need to run your code, but you donâ€™t want to worry about provisioning or managing servers. Which of the following AWS services would you choose? ","explanation":"Lambda is a Serverless technology that allows you to run your code without provisioning a computing infrastructure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/","title":"About Lambda"}],"answers":[{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":true},{"id":"2e31cdf7daad1ca06d6642765fa13252","text":"VMware Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"a31cc98c-2146-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following scenarios demand the use of an egress-only Internet gateway?","explanation":"An egress-only Internet gateway is used for IPv6 addresses only. It allows outbound communication from instances in your VPC to the Internet, and prevents the Internet from initiating connection with the instances.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/egress-only-internet-gateway.html","title":"Egress-Only Internet Gateways"}],"answers":[{"id":"9e839253188e9d5f95d2e2278c3bad32","text":"Allowing communication from the Internet and preventing communication to the Internet over IPv4","correct":false},{"id":"350b0f16434bcd3e211471390f1d840b","text":"Allowing communication from the Internet and preventing communication to the Internet over IPv6","correct":false},{"id":"5be0953999314fd060740ef201866d64","text":"Allowing communication to the Internet and preventing communication from the Internet over IPv6","correct":true},{"id":"01fc59aa00d3c5c5c0ffff43b05a22a0","text":"Allowing communication to the Internet and preventing communication from the Internet over IPv4","correct":false}]},{"id":"e64254c2-1a50-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services, which includes Amazon VPC. By comparison, the customer is responsible for what goes in the AWS Cloud. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses), security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic), and network ACLs as additional layers of security.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"3ca98dadd6a9bcbe75450331cd449df5","text":"Network access control lists (network ACLs)","correct":true},{"id":"97fd1873341a4d886cd8a23614cef0ff","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Service","correct":false},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true}]}]}}}}
